In this session,
we are going to discuss like have a walk
through of audit balance control
framework,
which is a common reusable framework
across all the assets of June 2, June 3.
OK,
so this audit balance control framework
is just an execution frame,
execution control framework which ensures
our data loads or accurate, consistent.
OK,
so I hear what So in the audit process,
we'll have it like it will just check
whether all the records that are coming
from the source are properly loaded into
into the target or not.
And if there are any errors and any
balance checks,
all these things that will just audit all
these record counts in the job run stats
table balance implies it's just do a
amount aggregated sum check of both
source data and target data after the
load.
And then also if we have any COM checks
that that falls under this balance
reconciliation,
it will also do that control.
Control implies that it it manages the
restartability rerun all these operations.
OK,
so let me show you the data model of ABC
here.
Whatever the tables that are highlighted
in red, right,
All these are metadata tables and the
green ones are runtime tables.
So here we are building a framework using
these tables and we are making insertions
before the load and updations after the
load based upon the load happened.
Can you zoom in a bit this?
Yeah, I'll, I'll zoom in.
The ping tables are the metadata tables
and green ones are the correct run
runtime tables.
So we have to make manual entries into
the metadata tables first before
triggering our task loop and green ones
would be automatically loaded as part of
the framework.
OK so the first one is batch metadata
table.
This will hold the information related to
the batch batch batch run.
So here as of now we have domains right?
Domains is over domain source and layer.
So we have a batch at domain source and
layer level.
For example, if you consider broker,
so our first asset asset is broker domain.
So we have a batch for CMPM.
This broker domain tables are getting
data from CMPM.
CMPM is the source,
broker is the domain and layer is the
data domain.
In Snowflake we have different layers.
In zone 2 we have two layers 1 is data
domain layer and the the one is
functional layer.
Currently all our assets falls like falls
under these like in the future state data
model all our tables are currently in
domain only.
So all our tables are in data domain
layer.
So for this broker tables and whatever
the data that is coming from the CMPM and
these being loaded to broker domain
tables in the data domain layer is
considered as a single batch.
So you're getting my point right.
Source domain and layer,
these three combination is considered as
A1 batch here.
OK.
So for broker,
the source would be CMPM application name.
Sorry,
domain name would be like broker domain.
Broker domain tables can be loaded from
multiple sources,
but one of the sources for the broker
domain is CMPM.
As of now, it's just an example.
Yeah.
So for that example,
source name would be CMPM,
domain name would be broker and
application layer name,
What would be data domain and target zone
would be zone 2.
Target zone would be zone 2.
OK, yeah, go on.
Zone 2, I have few tables of CCO handy.
I'll show you that entry.
All these all these are previous entries
or like which I have worked earlier in
June, July Sure, sure.
So if you see here in the batch metadata,
in the batch metadata table won't happen.
OK, I'm not able to run this.
Sure, let me open one UT document.
I mean the credentials are rotated for
that.
This the DP visualizer I'm not able to
connect.
Sure,
I haven't checked in since the moment.
Showing an error.
Maybe the username got expired?
Yeah.
So here if you see for CCO there are two
domains like CCO data is being loaded to
two domains account and contract.
So there will be 1 batch for account and
CCO data domain layer and CCO contract
data domain layer there would be another
batch.
So now I'm I'm showing you the batch
related to CCO and account and data
domain layer.
So batch ID like batch it is just normal
auto auto increment value.
Batch name is just John to batch,
CCO account.
Batch description we can follow like
there is some standard to have for all
these columns.
All those details are already present in
LLD.
We can go through it.
This is just active indicator e-mail ID.
Source name is CCO,
domain name is account,
application name is not.
We're not using this column.
Application layer name is rated domain
and application dependency name is CCO
and application dependency application
source batch IDs 387.
So actually here our zone 2 table load is
dependent on zone 1 table load, right?
Which which is whose application name is
CCO.
So CCO to zone one domain load is
presented by CCO and its corresponding
batch ID, Zone 1, batch ID,
this is the zone 1 batch ID and then this
is our target zone,
Zone 2 frequency scheduling,
Dole Stone branch and these two these
these are just dummy values as of now.
Once we have the scheduler in place,
then we have to update these values with
the actual values load schedule time and
load expected completed time like this.
And there's our audit columns.
Audit columns are just like whenever we
make entry into any table,
all these 4 columns would be inserted
audit create daytime,
audit update daytime would be just
current timestamp values at UTC and audit
create daytime or just current users.
Kiosks is not our column.
It's related to zone one.
It's optional for zone 2 and zone 3.
OK, And then job metadata OK.
Your batch metadata is that And then
coming to job metadata table.
So for each batch we have multiple tables,
right?
So for each table we'll have entry in,
we have to make entry into the job
metadata table.
OK,
let me show you the entries and the job
metadata table.
So for this particular batch,
I have account party address is is one of
the tables.
So for this I have made entry like this.
This is auto increment value.
And this is just your name.
You have to be very cautious while you're
giving the job name because we would be
using this job name while we are fetching
the job ID and the logic of IPC framework,
OK and then job description is that 2
indicator and this is the batch ID 434.
This is belonging to this batch.
And then table name,
schema name and then database name,
job load type, workflow name.
So we'll have two workflows here.
Batch will have one workflow,
Job will have one workflow.
All the job level workflows would be
integrated inside the batch level task
screen.
So this batch level task flow is used in
the scheduling tool.
So from the scheduling tool,
the batch level task flow would be
directly triggered and then inside these
all the job level task flows would be
integrated as a sub task flow and it will
trigger all these tasks.
All the job level task flows will get
triggered.
So here workflow name represents job
level workflow name and this is the
wrapper workflow name which is nothing
but the batch level task flow workflow
name and count threshold indicator,
Amount balance indicator,
these two fields related to the balance
reconciliation.
So if you have any count threshold check
indicator for your particular table then
keep it as Y otherwise N amount balance
check indicator.
If you have any amount columns or any
anything related to quantity check,
amount balancing check,
then you have to keep it as Y else it
would be N.
This just skips if if we don't have any
balancing balance checks,
then it will just skip the balance
reconciliation process.
That's it.
OK.
And then audit columns so as to target
layer.
It's just 112 dated option.
OK, So when you say no,
then then reconciliation will not check,
right?
That get count.
Yeah,
it is handled at the ID and C task flow
level.
We will pass this indicators to the task
flow and there it will check if any one
of these is why then only or if both of
these are and then balance reconciliation
will be happened.
Otherwise in all other cases,
if any one of these is why or both of
these is why balance reconciliation would
be run.
Yeah, for the amount 1, right,
we need to specific,
we need to specify the exact table level,
which column has the amount and then that
will check, right?
Yeah,
for that we have a separate table that
balance sheet cancellation metadata.
We have a separate table.
I can show that.
No, no, that's fine.
That's fine.
We can continue.
I'll show that anywhere and then ETL data
ingestion metadata table.
So this table is relevant to John 2 and
John 3.
So there are few changes in these tables.
They have added few 3 columns I guess
very recently.
Those changes are not yet updated,
but I'll just cover all the changes as
possible in the end for now.
So here what is the significance of this
table is each like our zone 2 is
dependent on zone one right?
So we have to proceed with our table load
only only when our all our source tables
load is successfully completed in the
zone 1 correct?
How zone 2 load is dependent on Zone 1 is.
If any one of the table load is completed
in the Zoneman batch, it would be marked.
Its status would be marked finally as
partial.
If all the table loads is completed
successfully then it would be completed.
This is how their framework is.
Zone 1 framework is if the final status
of the zone 1 batch run is either partial
or completed then it is OK to start our
zone 2 batch.
This is a.
This is the assumption that we took
forever.
Zone 2 batch run OK.
So whenever my whenever the zone status
is partial then in the case our source
table run,
job run might be successful or failure.
We we are not sure right.
So for that reason in order to check each
table's status,
job in time all these things we have
created we have added this table.
This table consists of our target batch
ID which is from the batch metadata table,
target job ID which is from the job
metadata table, target table name,
source name,
source table name is active indicator and
audit fields.
Along with these my like our only one
source table can be present in multiple
schemas or databases right?
So in order to avoid the duplicate source
table name issue,
our team has added three more columns
called database name,
schema name and source object name.
These three they have added in order to
uniquely identify our source table name
from the job metadata table.
OK so like you will get all the details
in the logic.
OK so this is a significance it will hold
all the source and target table names if
you see here.
So here for our batch we have only one
source.
There is target batch ID, target job ID,
target table name,
source name is CCO source table name is
address T,
address T is active indicator and all it
fails.
That's it.
Basically this table shows our sources
basically, right?
So correct.
Which all source are involved in one
particular job run, correct Or what?
All source load should be completed
before our target to start,
I mean before our load to start, correct?
So this is different from this ETL data
injection source window, right?
That is the runtime table which uses this
metadata table.
This is different.
This is the static table,
that is the runtime table.
That runtime table uses this table.
OK then coming to the job role master.
It's like a a high level table which will
holds all the rules.
Basically all the rules first like if we
want to do any like if we want to like do
any assign any rule to any of our columns
in our table first that rule should be
present in this job rule master.
Then only we we would be able to add that
rule to work job.
So for example, null check,
null check is one of the rules.
So if we want to do a null check for a
specific column in our table,
first we have to add a rule called null
check in this table.
And then only we have to assign that rule
ID to our table.
This is the job rule assignment table.
I'll,
I'll cover this also and then I'll show
you the example job rule assignment table.
So here job rule assignment ID is just
outer increment value.
Job ID it's coming from the job metadata
table Rule ID is coming from this rule,
Job rule master table validation type if
it is free or post and then target column
name,
what is the column target table column
name and then pattern available.
If there is any pattern we have to give
it as Y otherwise N and pattern name
RCVIT code error,
error message text is that all these
things?
So whatever rule that we want to assign
to any of our columns,
we have to add that rule first here and
then use that rule here.
Let me show you the example.
So here null check is having the rule ID
one.
The rules copies at the column level and
the audit fails here.
For this particular job there are the
three DQ checks account party ID,
account address identifier,
address type code.
So all these are DQ checks.
Validation types are just DQ checks and
then pattern is not available for this
and then error CVRT code is given as
error CVRT code can be either critical or
informational.
So based upon the error CVRT code final
status would be dependent.
So if there if if there is any column
which fails the rule which is marked as
critical then it then our final job
status would be automatically marked as
failed.
If it is informational our job status
finally updated as succeeded.
But a warning notification would be sent
out for informational type of rules OK
error message would be null values found
OK and then to indicator and audit fails
and rule ID, job ID OK.
After that we have just to repeat once
again.
So job rule master would be the one where
you will have all the specific
validations mentioned,
generic validations.
And then the job proof assignment,
we will have the job ID mentioned which
is corresponding to each of the job.
And then if we,
we if we are using any of these rules,
right?
Correct, correct.
So if,
if we can use the same rule ID for all
the jobs across all the assets,
all the domains,
if we have any new rule like date format
check,
then we have to add that date format
check first in this rule master and then
use that rule ID here in,
in the job rule assignment trip.
This is for all the DQ checks, right?
This is for all the DQ checks once,
like whatever the rule,
it would be only inserted into this table
only once across all the domains.
OK, OK.
If anything extra there,
we need to make a entry into that and
then we could check against that, right?
We have to first check whether the tool
is already present or not,
but it's present anyway.
We need it to get the rule ID.
Whenever we are adding it,
it will ask you about the rule ID here.
So yeah,
we have the last two columns of rule ID
and job ID.
I just want to show you the balance
reconciliation metadata as well.
Yeah, balance reconciliation metadata.
Here we will give all the details of the
columns, threshold values,
threshold types,
all this details related to the
reconciliation process we have here in
the metadata.
I'll show you the example directly.
So here for this particular job,
we have around 7 balance reconciliation.
All these are reconciliation amount.
All these are amount columns only.
So first column is reconciliation metric
ID which is auto increment value.
This is the description of the balance
reconciliation metric and then balancing
type is amount here.
So all these things we are doing for
amount but if you have any other thing
like count then we have to give it as a
count.
So those two target layer is just defined
to Dom to data domain target,
database name, target schema name,
target table name and the columns on
which we are doing the reconciliation
target column name, regions source pass,
source query,
target query we are not choosing them.
These are optional for us.
And threshold type name would be
percentage.
It can be percentage or value for like.
In this case we are asked like for CCU
policy table that threshold type is
percentage.
We can directly compare the out of
balance value directly against a value.
Also here we are comparing it against a
5%.
So you know right Like amount,
amount columns.
If we are checking the source and target
amount and the difference if it is not
equal to 0, if it is other than 0,
then we'll compare that value against
this percentage.
If it is less than 5 percentage then then
we can like we can accept this and we can
mark the job status as success.
But if it is above the threshold value,
then we will mark it as failure.
Job status is failed.
That's it.
Here we'll provide the threshold value
and then is active indicator,
active audit fields and job ID.
That's it.
OK, what is file, File related tables.
We're not using any file related tables.
We're done with the metadata tables.
Let's focus on this runtime tables,
batch run stats tables very OK Batch run
stats table is just it it,
it holds the run details of each batch
run.
OK,
we have batch details in the batch
metadata table, right?
So using those details,
it will make an entry into this table.
And here only we will you know this,
we will handle the restart,
rerun all these runs.
Also we will be handling in the batch run
starts preload only.
OK,
this table actually this like I heard I
got to know that this table structure is
slightly changed and we are having a
separate table to hold the sourcing
windows,
sourcing window details of the source
tables.
OK,
I I don't have them handy table structure,
but I'll I'll see I'll see the tracker
ones.
But for now I'm just giving you the
details high level for this.
So here batch run ID is the primary key,
which is a UUID column.
Batch ID would be coming from the batch
metadata table.
Execution run ID would be the UUID column.
For each execution run,
we'll have a separate UUID and instance
ID.
We are not using database name is just a
database name table name.
We are not using sourcing start date time.
Sourcing end date time,
we would be populating these values.
These sourcing end time would be actually
based basically the zone one source and
zone 1 patch end time.
OK.
And then batch start time is just current
time stamp.
What is solving start date TF daytime it
is.
So if it's first time, first time load,
it will usually OK.
So for the first time as of now,
I'm just giving you the details related
to the incremental load.
So yeah,
for the first time incremental load entry
would be made management into this
batched and stressed table with the value
that is as per the requirement.
So basic.
So let me give you some details about
about history and catheter load.
Just an example,
so from Teradata to Snowflake,
we will be doing the historical load and
then cash flow and then we'll start with
incremental load, right.
So if we are doing historical load,
we will start from the low end date 1900
to some August 31st till August 31st.
We are doing it as part of historical
load.
So the data would be very huge.
It might take 10 days like for example it
took 10 days till September 10th the load
happened.
So the data from that day from September
1st to September 10th is done as part of
catch up load and then first time
incremental we are planning to have it on
from September 8th.
In order to like avoid the data loss,
we are doing it two days prior to the
catch up load.
Historical load and catch upload would be
done directly from the Teradata to
Snowflake via demagrated tool using
demagrated tool via zone 1 iceberg tables
OK and incremental table.
Incremental data would be from the actual
source system to zone 1 iceberg table and
then zone 2 table OK.
This is how it happens.
So first time incremental the date is is
as per the requirement.
OK,
so it would be a manual entry for the
first time.
As this batch run stats table is splitted
into two tables batch run stats and batch
sourcing stats.
We are holding all these sourcing,
start date time sourcing and date time
details into a separate table called
batch sourcing stats.
This is a very recent new change.
So we the reason behind this splitting is
earlier we are under.
We have created this framework under the
assumption that each zone 2 batch run is
dependent on a single zone 1 batch run.
OK but later the requirement came where
zone 2 batch is dependent on multiple
zone 1 batch run.
So for that purpose we have splitted this
table because job sourcing and time will
hold the batch end time of the zone 1
batch.
So if we have multiple values we should
have multiple entries right?
So in order to have only single run for a
batch run,
we we are using this batch run stats
table to see the batch run level details
and for sourcing star window in this,
we are keeping them into a separate table
called bad sourcing stats.
There's a new table, new change,
but I'm just giving you this information.
OK.
And after that, yeah,
just just that question still.
Yes,
first time for the intermental you said
it will be manually updated for the
second time where this would be sourcing
start time would be the previous sourcing
end time.
So second run.
In the second run,
whatever the sourcing end end sourcing
start time would be the previous sourcing
end time and sourcing end time would be
again June 1 batch end times.
OK, if you didn't get,
I'll give you an example of times so
previously completed.
How much ever was the Max for the first
sourcing date?
OK, add would come for the first time,
I'll give you,
I will give you the values only then
you'll get in.
So for the first,
before the first time incremental,
our zone,
zone one load has completed at 1:00 PM,
at 12:00 PM, twelve AM, 12:30 AM,
let's say today, 12:30 AM,
our Zone 1 batch has completed on
September 8th, let's say September 8th.
So first time incremental date we
considered some some September 1st,
let's say or September 5th, 5th, 2,
eighth September 8th would be my June 1
batch end time,
which is my first batch end time.
OK,
so this isn't the time window for the
first day incremental load.
Now coming to the next day,
whatever the 8th 12:30 AM is there right
batch end time previous days yesterday's.
So that would be my sourcing start date
time,
which is September 8th would be mine
sourcing start date time and sourcing end
date time would be September 9th,
12:30 AM is the sourcing end time,
which is the batch end time of the June 1
batch today's batch room.
OK, how, how will this get updated?
Maybe it is an ETL job.
I didn't think we have.
We have logic already in place in the
batch run search preload.
We we'll, we,
we can check it like I'll just give you
the walkthrough of the also.
Sure, sure.
OK,
let me quickly complete these runtime
tables.
I think we are on time on top of the
table.
OK, job run stats table.
So here job run ID is the foreign key of
this column of this table.
OK, so the primary key of this table,
which is a UUID value execution run ID is
coming from the batch run stats table.
Job instance ID is optional for us.
Job ID is coming from the job metadata
table.
Job static time is current time stamp.
Job end date time end time is the current
time stamp.
It will be updated in the post.
Load status would be started in the
before the load and either completed or
failed after the run.
It depends on the state,
target database name, table name,
schema and all these are related to Sir
and the.
All these are the counts and record count.
Balancing flag is nothing but it compares
it will be.
Why?
If the source and target record counts
aggregated sum would be same.
If it is same then it would be why?
Else it would be N and aggregate columns
and extra hours.
You'll get to know this when we are like
like going through the actual design
framework.
OK, for now,
just remember this as the counts.
Sure, sure.
Yeah.
And job rule execution log.
So this table is related to the job role
assignment.
So here whatever the job rules that are
assigned to our table, we have entries.
So for each column we have assigned rules
in the job role assignment table.
Right?
For each job role assignment,
we have entries into this table before
the load and after the load.
However, the like load happens.
Depending upon the result,
this table gets updated with either error
message or execution details.
OK so whether the rule is completed,
whether the rule is passed or failed or
in case if it is failed,
what is the error?
How many records got errored out while
comparing this?
Like while validating this rule,
if it is successfully passed then it will
give execution details like everything is
passed out, no null values found out,
0 null values found like the the details
would be like it.
It's kind of a log table, OK.
And then before the job and entry will be
made after the job the IT will be updated.
It will be updated,
correct job rule error.
It will be there.
ETL data injection sourcing window.
This is the table that you are talking
about while we were discussing it on ETL
data injection metadata.
So using the source table names we will
get we'll get all the details of the so
like all the sourcing window details.
So our like our zone 2 tables are
dependent Zone 1 table job runs right.
So we will take the sourcing window also
based upon their job end times job like
their load.
So basically here sourcing end time we
are taking at the source job and like we
are taking the job end time of the source
table.
So here we are taking the and like taking
the source window at the source table
level.
So it's not uniform for all the source
tables it it would be different for
different source tables.
So if I'm having 22 source tables for my
one target table, it will fetch,
it will create the sourcing window for
each source table based upon its run.
OK,
so we'll have all these details like this,
This is this execution and ID, batch ID,
job ID, all these are foreign keys.
And then target table M,
source table M and this is the source job
run ID.
What is the job run that we are
considering?
That run ID would be placed here and the
job status sourcing start time would be
just prior like previous sourcing end
time.
Just like in batch.
This is also same sourcing end time would
be the source job end time yeah.
And then all these there are so many like
things that are considered while we are
populating these values.
We can discuss them in the logic or work
through.
And job error status.
Job error status is a kind of a log table.
In case of any error,
any failure at any step,
the entry would be made into this table
before we are updating the status in the
job run stats as failed.
So in case of any error in the during the
job run our final state our the state
final status in the job run stats table.
This this is the job level table job run
stats.
So we will we would be updating the
status to fail along with that failure
rotation would be making an entry into
this job error status.
So in case if your job fails,
check this job error stats table and
you'll get the information related to
your error.
OK.
If it is execution error,
then you forget but framework related
errors, right Those would be captured.
Got it.
OK.
And then job will error detail.
Job will error detail.
This is this is also related to rules,
job rules only.
But here we'll have details at the column
level, source record and column level.
So for each source record.
So if we have applied if we have assigned
2 rules 2 rules that means we we are
doing null check for two columns then in
that case our each record would be
validated twice right?
So all those records that so a single
source record is having issue is is
failed for the 2 rules assigned by us.
So then that single record would be
transposed into two records at the column
level.
So for this column one this record is
failed and it's source UID is this value
like that.
So this will holds information at the
record column level OK.
Whereas this holds information at the job
rule assignment level.
Job rule assignment level this is at the
record column level,
source record column level OK and then
balance reconciliation starts.
It will host information if there are
multiple records which has failed that
rule all those will come under job rule
error detail record.
So if 3 records,
3 records failed out of which fast record
is failed for both 2nd and 3rd record
failed for only one,
one OK one each then we'll it will result
in four records here and the job will
error detail.
First record would be transposed in two
records because it failed for two records
it failed 2 so 2 records and 2nd record
failed only one.
Then third third entry would be that and
final only 1 so 4 entries.
So this is the job will error detail.
What about the other OK table?
This would be there in the other table.
So here 3 records.
I told you right,
all the three records failed at column
one.
Only the fast record failed at column two.
OK, this is the example that I'm giving.
So all the three of the error records out
of which all the three records failed at
the rule 1 which is which is assigned to
column one and only the first record
failed at column two.
That means three we have job rules,
2 job rules.
We have assigned rules to two columns,
correct?
Yes, I'll, I'll take this.
The two entries will be there in the
other 122 entries will be there and the
statistics will will show like for the
first rule,
33 columns or three records are failed,
right?
So 3 records are found with null values
and 2nd for the second rule,
1 record with one record is failed with
with like 1 record found with null values.
Like it depends on the error message.
So I'm just taking null.
Yeah, display,
display SO2 entries here and four entries
in the other place 4 reach there.
Yeah, balance reconciliation status,
it holds all the details related to the
balance reconciliation.
Balance reconciliation metric ID is a
UUID column and metric ID is it is a
foreign.
All these three are the foreign case
which would be coming from the before
like tables that I have explained already.
Valuation rate is the date on which we
are specifically doing this valuation.
If we are doing daily loads,
we don't need to assign any value for
this.
If we are specifically doing then only
this value be populated.
This is the source value.
So if we are doing any amount metric kind
of sum,
then source value will hold the
aggregated sum of the source amount
amount column and target value will hold
the aggregated sum of the target column
value and then balancing flag.
So this source value and target value
this difference would be our out of
balance value.
If it is 0,
then out of out of balance value then
balancing flag and threshold flag would
be Y.
If it is not zero,
then balancing flag would be N and then
it will be checked that makes the
threshold value.
If it is within threshold then threshold
flag would be Y else it would be N and
audit fails.
OK file.
We are not we don't have files.
OK, can we yes join that call.
We can continue it or post that call.
No,
which which we have a call right And
Auguste asked us to join right.
I think that is related to history part.
If you if you are part of history part,
then you can join Otherwise you can
ignore yeah.
I mean,
if we can schedule another call with you
tomorrow,
I I should have one last call maybe for
explaining the code part.
You can schedule it 415 wincy today
itself because maybe not sure tomorrow
onwards if I'm occupied right or be able
to.
We have a 4X4 that is way OK.
430 is OK.
What?
430 is OK for you?
Yeah.
Yeah, it's OK.
I I just want to close this KT today.
That's it.
OK, perfect.
Yeah.
We'll move it 4:30 then.
Yeah.
You can download this and share it with
the team.
Yeah.
Where exactly can I find it in this data
model or in in LM?
I'll, I'll send it to you.
You can share it with the team.
OK.
LED updates are still in progress.
Like that's OK.
I think we don't like make any changes.
If you want to see, just take a copy.
OK.
Sure.
I'll share it with you.
Sure.
I sure.
Thank you.
We'll join.
Yeah, sure.
Yes, Yeah, this side exactly.
Can I share this section for this?
I'm joined a little late for that some I
don't know.
Yeah, Vinci will be sharing that.
Yeah, I I I'll share.
OK.
Sure.
Thank you.
Thank you, Tim.
Thank you, Aisha, this is really helpful.
Yeah, Thank you.
Thank you.
Thanks so much.
They don't have the options.